[
   {
      "question":"Q1.What is the capital of Bangladesh ?",
      "optionOne":"Chittagong",
      "optionTwo":"Dhaka",
      "correctanswer":"Dhaka"
   },
   {
      "question":"Q2.What is the national fruit of Bangladesh ?",
      "optionOne":"Jackfruit",
      "optionTwo":"Mango",
      "correctanswer":"Jackfruit"
   },
   {
      "question":"Q3.What is swift ?",
      "optionOne":"A Bird",
      "optionTwo":"Software",
      "correctanswer":"A Bird"
   },
   {
      "question":"Q4.What is MAC OS ?",
      "optionOne":"Linux",
      "optionTwo":"OS",
      "correctanswer":"OS"
   },
   {
      "question":"Q5.How many fingers do we have ?",
      "optionOne":"20",
      "optionTwo":"10",
      "correctanswer":"20"
   },
   {
      "question":"Q6.What is skype ?",
      "optionOne":"Social Media",
      "optionTwo":"News Reader",
      "correctanswer":"Social Media"
   },
   {
      "question":"Q7.Who was Einstain ?",
      "optionOne":"A Doctor",
      "optionTwo":"A Scientist",
      "correctanswer":"A Scientist"
   },
   {
      "question":"Q8.How many faces a brick has ?",
      "optionOne":"4",
      "optionTwo":"6",
      "correctanswer":"6"
   },
   {
      "question":"Q9.Which one can travel faster ?",
      "optionOne":"Light",
      "optionTwo":"Sound",
      "correctanswer":"Light"
   },
   {
      "question":"Q10.What is the sign of USD ?",
      "optionOne":"@",
      "optionTwo":"$",
      "correctanswer":"$"
   }
]
